letter from loreto
john kerry occu is the only guy who's in
prison does george bush
and ira and and uh...
they didn't bush in gonzalez's and by
the j by the who is now a
he uh... judge on the ninth circuit
court of appeals believe it or not
and john you who've mind-boggling lee is
a professor of law i believe professor
in any case the university of california
berkeley
you mentioned in class from a guy who
like
help your country
torture people and destroyed the
recognition your country
i have a real problem with that
anyhow and dick cheney and don rumsfeld
and and kinda lisa race the is basically
about twenty people in the bush
administration
who put together this whole uh... let's
torture people plan let's violate the
geneva conventions let's do what they
actually
the executed white the united states
executed japanese soldiers for doing in
the philippines let's do what the
nuremberg tribunals prosecuted nazis for
doing after world war two
let's do that ourselves
and become pariahs make the muslim world
think there were
earlier war against them in the one guy
who had the the intestinal fortitude to
stand up and say no this isn't right i'm
gonna go to the press with this
and blow the whistle john carrey our
group
he is in prison
anne wrote a letter is amazing letter
it's uh... it's reprinted in many places
over the web i got my copy from
from uh... firedoglake dot com which has
a
you can actually see the the original
and you can print out the tax bill that
separate out the tech so i sure would be
this is his letter
it because they had provides amazing
inside a life in prison
uses greetings of the federal
correctional institute loreto
pennsylvania i arrived here at the very
twenty eight twenty thirteen to serve a
thirty-month sentence
for violating the intelligence
identities protection act of nineteen
eighty two
at least that's what the government
wants people to believe
in truth this is my punishment for
blowing the whistle on the c_i_a_'s
illegal torture program
and for telling the public that torture
was official u_s_ government policy
but that's a different story purpose
this letters to tell you about prison
life
at my formal sentencing hearing in
january the judge the prosecutors in my
attorneys all agree that i would serve
my son's in laredo as federal work
camp
when i arrived our rush to my suraj
surprise the corrections officer of the
ceceo
uh... they're also call hacks
the ceo who process me said that the
bureau of prisons are deemed me a quote
threat to the public safety and quote
and so i would serve the entire sons in
an actual prison rather than at the camp
little friendlier place
processing took about an hour included
fingerprinting um a mug shot
by third after f_b_i_ marshals
by four th d_n_a_ sample are quite
comprehensive strip search
as good a pair of betty brown pants to
brown shirts to two pairs of underwear
two pairs of socks
ever achieve symbols
by own clothes were box to mail to my
wife
the ceo christians officer then led me
to the steel bonk
in central unit in walked away didn't
know what to do so i took a nap
buysell is more like a cubicle made out
of concrete
built to hold four men meinhold six most
of this whole debate
by cell mates include to dominican
serving twenty four in twenty years
sentences for drugs
a mexican surrey fifteen years for drugs
a porter recon serving seven-and-a-half
years for drug conspiracy
and the former auditor of cuyahoga
county ohio
who's doing a long sentence for
corruption
there'll be some guys me actually enjoy
each other's company
the prison populations much like you
might expect loretta has six thirteen
hundred and sixty nine prisoners and
ever call myself an inmate on a prisoner
about fifty percent of black thirty
percent hispanic twenty percent are
white
of the white prisoners muster pedophiles
with personal stories that would make
you sick to your stomach
the rest of the white prisoners every
here are here for drugs
except for a dozen or so grand ponzi
schemes
of the thirteen hundred and sixty nine
prisoners forty have college degrees in
six mister masters degrees
the g_t_e_ program is robust
but when i volunteer to teach a class my
counselor shouted
denning carry ako up allies you teach an
acting class i did i'd ask you to teach
in f in class
sana janitor in the chapel an inc five
dollars and twenty five cents a month
they capture chow all
is the most difficult experience my
first few days were shy set
my first day
to erin's complete covered in tattoos
walked up to be nast
at your profile
nope i said
annual faggot
and he had good paper
i didn't know what this meant
it turned out that i had to get a copy
of my formal sentencing documents to
prove that i was a child molester
i did that
and was welcomed by the areas who are
really area and spit more accurately
self-importance hillbillies
the cafeteria is very formally divided
there is a table for the whites with
good paper a section of the table for
the native americans
a section of a table for people
belonging to a certain italian american
stereotypical subculture
to take in quotes two tables for the
moslems for tables for the pedophiles
and all the remaining tables for the
blacks and hispanics
we don't all he is the same time but
he's tables more less reserved as i
described
violence as an immature problem since i
arrived there but maybe a half dozen
fights
almost always over what television show
to watch the choices are pretty much set
in stone trainee espy on m_t_v_ v_h_-one
b_e_t_ in univision
and watch tv since i got your sister
worth the trouble
otherwise violence is in the problem
most of the guys in here of
work their way did down to a low
security prison from medium or maximum
and they don't want to go back
and also had some luck in this regard
by reputation preceded me
anna rumor got started that i was a
c_i_a_ get bad
the aaron's whispered that i was a
moslem hotter
to go out to the moslems on the strength
of my turbans ever big language skills
uh... well time statement of support
from louis farrakhan
uh... instead the moslems applauded me
as a champion of muslim human rights
meanwhile the italians have taken a
liking me is unpatriotic as they are
and i have a visceral dislike of the
f_b_i_ which they do as well
i have good relations with the blacks
because it helps several of them right
connotation appeals or letters to judges
i don't charge anything for it
and hispanics respected because my cell
mates
who are present a myriad of latin drug
gangs
have told them that
have told them to so far so good
you know i think close to a problem pat
has been from the c_e_o_ so this is the
correction officers
by first arrived after about four days i
heard an announcement but i was told to
dread
uh... to react to report to the
lieutenant's office immediately very
quickly i gave my wife's phone number to
a friend asked new caller if for some
reason
i was sent to the s_ h_ u_ special
housing unit olson is the whole
uh...
or solitary confined
i have no name wrong but this coming
happens all the time
when i got those ads office i was
archerd into the office of s_i_s_ the
special investigative service
this is the prison version of every
police departments detective bureau
i sought a desk a copy of my book the
reluctance spy as well as dvd copies
of all the documentaries that billion
the ceo showed me a picture of an air of
dinos guy aspect
i responded that i'd met in a day
earlier but our conversation was limited
to a nice to meet you
well the ceo said
this guy is the uncle the times square
bomber
answering many call the number of
pakistan's
uh... pakistanis are part of the meeting
and was told to kill me
i told the c_r_ ceo that i could kill
you have my phone is off five four
hundred and twenty-five pounds compared
to my six one two fifty
the c_e_o_ said they were looking to
ship them out so i should stay away from
him
the more i thought about this more this
made no sense
by one of the uncle of the times square
bomber being a low security prison
usually in max maximum
so i ask my muslim friends to check him
out
it turns out that he's an iraqi kurds
from buffalo new york
use the imam of the moscow there which
also have to be demoss where the
lackawanna seven worship black one seven
return for conspiracy could terrorism
the f_b_i_ pressured him to testify
against his paresh years
he refusing got five years for
obstruction of justice
is to use a religious freedom groups of
rallied his defense he had nothing to do
with terrorism
in the meanwhile
the s_i_s_ told him
but i had made a call to washington
after we had met and uh... i had been
instructed to kill a bell
we both laughed at the ham handedness by
which the s_i_s_
try to get us to attack each other
if we had they would it we'd we would
have spent the rest of
our senses in the s_h_ u_n_ solitary
instead were friendly we exchange
greetings in arabic and english in we
chat
illinois they're from a head of the
c_e_o_'s is about two weeks after i
arrived at get a good deal a male here
in prison i answer every letter i get
monday through friday prisoners
uh... the other and for the u_n_ ceo's
office for mail call one
seat female c_e_o_ butchers my name
every time she says it
when she does me and mail call i here go
to your account cara cruel karaoke
emily other issues
one day after mail call it passed in the
hall
she stopped and so you be an afro whose
name i campgrounds i responded curiosity
she set up i just call you after its
has walked away from those what was a
classic
isaiah i said they have white trash is
more like it
and a dollar later for ceos the c_e_o_'s
discernible to ourselves trashing all of
a worldly possessions in my first
shakedown
lesson learned
ceo st aside subhuman we have to show
them respect even when it's not a
you're listening to the trial mark munro
my hasn't come hardman dot com for audio
and video archive there's just a sense
of the others including his address so
sure within weeks
come back from the break about five
minutes
so i can tell you that uh... because
not just had a light this letter so
touched and so and it's just
that the other guy who by the way if you
write a letter he will respond to your
quest bonnet within several times
is don siegel money
and on suman as america's political
prisoner you can do you can get don
siegel man's information for a free
dashing don dot org
and i'm pretty sure that they have his
address in prison over there
out this is john carrey ako he's the guy
who outed bushes torture program and now
the torturers went to prison
nobody from the bush administration went
to prison
the people who devastated the who
destroyed the reputation this country
didn't go to prison the people who
killed people didn't go to prison
the people who caused
you know hundreds of people be stocking
guantanamo on prosecutable because their
confessions were a pix track that under
torture so they're meaningless they can
be used in court of law
and then there may not be true
none of those people went to prison
but john carrey aqua did a nice is
all right our ceo cios more next time if
you'd like to drop me a line i can be
reached a john kerry oxo
seven nine six three seven dash zero
eight three
p_o_ box one thousand at sea isle around
a leora loreto
loreto pennsylvania one five nine
or zero best regards from really read
road job
prana slaughter
as i said you can find it over at uh...
firedoglake wilder there'll be a
linked to it uh... tomorrow and in our
uh... dances daily stacking
you'll get all that information in our
newsletter and all the kind of stuff if
you want
track it down but
i'd just thought that i was
just absolute that uh...